最新电影大片首发 请访问
新气息论坛 www.xinqixi.com
-嗨  -嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
几位
How many?
2位
Two.
听着  我想办理一个保险柜  你能搞定吗
Listen, I wanted to get a safe deposit box. Can you do that for me?
办好了  保险柜的使用时间
Okay. Your box will be available
是银行开门后一小时
any time from an hour after opening
到关门前半小时  这是钥匙
to 30 minutes before close. This is your key.
谢谢
Thank you.
还有  如果你开个支票账户的话
Oh, um, also, if you open a checking account,
就可享受保险柜95折优惠和免费透支保障
we'll give you 5% off the box along with free overdraft protection.
我还以为能送个烤面包机呢
Oh, here I was hopin' for a free toaster.
银行为什么要送烤面包机
Why would a bank give out free toasters?
早啊  马
Hello, Ma.
我正在给你点法式烤面包呢
I'm ordering you the French toast.
不用了  谢谢
No, thank you.
这位耐心的服务员  美琪
Our very patient waitress, Maggie,
都过来四次让我点餐了
well, at least it says Maggie on her name tag,
她名牌上写着美琪
has asked me to order four times.
你要是再不点餐也太没礼貌了
If I don't order at this point, it's just rude.
-我可以一会再来  -不  没事
-I can come back. -No, it's okay.
知道不  我来做决定就好
You know what? I'm making an executive decision.
-煎饼吧  -好的
-Pancakes. -Okay.
不要煎饼  我不喜欢煎饼  不要煎饼
No pancakes. I don't like pancakes. No pancakes.
你是共产党吗
What are you, a communist?
给我朋友来一份煎饼和煎鸡蛋
My friend'll have the pancakes and a fried egg.
我想吃蔬菜肉丁  不过要剁大的很碎才行  知道吗
I'm thinkin' hash, but only if it's like chunky style, okay?
喂  你要是给我点鸡蛋和煎饼  我肯定会踹死你
Listen, if you order me eggs and pancakes, I'm gonna kick your behind.
但是你总得吃早饭吧  这可是一天最重要的一餐
But you gotta eat breakfast. It's the most important meal of the day.
女士  忽略他吧  明白
Uh, ma'am, ignore everything he said, okay?
可别给我鸡蛋和煎饼
Don't bring me any eggs and pancakes.
给我杯咖啡就行了  多给他几个鸡蛋
Just bring me some coffee and bring him a couple eggs.
我不要鸡蛋  我想吃蔬菜肉丁
I don't want eggs. I want hash.
在上面放点鸡蛋也行
You know what, put a couple eggs on it.
再给他来点黑麦面包
Give him some rye toast, too.
我不要黑麦面包  我不喜欢黑麦面包
No rye toast for me. I don't like rye toast.
-来个煎饼  -不要煎饼
-And a pancake. -No pancakes.
来一点银元饼  有迷你的吗
Maybe a little silver-dollar one. You got the little baby ones?
不要煎饼  不要银元饼  也不要黑麦面包
No pancakes, no silver dollars, no rye toast.
我喜欢粗裸麦面包
I like pumpernickel.
我们也有粗裸麦烤面包
I do have pumpernickel. Pumpernickel toast.
-嘿  美琪  等等  -好的
-Hey, Maggie, wait. One more thing. -Yeah.
那个送你  在我们重逢之前你就随身带着吧
That's for you. You take that with you till we see each other again
以免你太想我了  好吗
in case you miss me too much, okay?
-你干嘛这么做  -怎么了
-Why you gotta do that? -What?
你干嘛跟她抛媚眼
Wink at the waitresses like that?
-服务员都喜欢我  -没人喜欢你
-Waitresses like me. -Nobody likes you.
-所以呢  -所以
-So? -So.
你查到什么了
What do ya got?
这是家安保不强的银行
So, it is a sleepy bank.
-能动手  -说得对
-Doable? -That's correct.
我早说过吧
I told you.
很多油炸圈饼啊
That is a lot of doughnuts.
蔬菜肉丁一会就来
I'll be right back with your hash.
美琪  你这火热的手工油炸圈饼  有什么名头吗
Maggie, your hot homemade doughnuts, they any good?
-周围三郡最好的  -我告诉你怎么做吧
-Best in three counties. -I'll tell you what you do.
我买三个圈饼
You bring us three of those bad boys.
帮我打好包  行吗
Put'em in a to-go box for us, all right?
-行  -谢谢
-All right. -Thank you.
好了  该走了
All right, time to make the move.
好吧  还指望她来勾引我呢
All right, there's gonna be some sirens in this bitch.
我去开启火灾警报器
I'm gonna go shake the weasel.
开启火灾警报器
Shake the weasel. Gonna go shake the weasel.
-嘿  早安  先生  过的好吗  -早安
-Hey. Good morning, sir. How are you? -Morning.
嘿  美琪
Hey, Maggie.
很抱歉  我这个朋友
I'm very sorry about my friend.
小时候脑袋被踢过
He was kicked in the head as a child.
-他没那么讨厌  -不  他就是
-He's really not that bad. -No, he is.
怎么回事
What's goin' on?
大家马上离开这里
Okay, I'm just gonna have you all exit the building.
可能是假警报  但是为了安全起见
It might be a false alarm, but just do it safely.
谢谢  谢谢合作
Thank you. Thank you.
大家都出去了吗  麻烦你出去吧
Is everybody out? I'm gonna need you to step outside.
知道了  美琪  我拉我朋友一起出去
All right, Maggie, I'm just gonna grab my friend.
-好吧  -我们去付账
-Okay. -We gotta pay our bill.
该走了
We should go.
这就是你给的小费
Is that all you're gonna leave for a tip?
15%呢  你只留了15%的小费
It's 15%. You leave 15%.
不  你起码该得30%
No, you gotta leave at least 30.
不行  15%是标准
No, you don't. 15% is standard.
我的美琪都要失业了  兄弟  别这么小气嘛
My Maggie's about to be out of a job, man. Don't be cheap.
好吧  这有五块  那有七块了
Okay, there's five. That's seven.
这还差不多  走吧
There you go. Come on.
好吧
All right.
干嘛  不是吧
What? No, you didn't.
-我就拿了  -真小气
-Yes, I did. -Oh, my God.
你觉得怎么样
How'd you say it?
从来没有从卖着最棒油炸圈饼的餐厅出来
Never rob a bank across from the diner
就去抢银行的吧
with the best doughnuts in three counties?
说得对
That's correct.
双龙出手
一周前
墨西哥  索诺拉
鲍比  帕皮在马厩里
Bobby. Papi's down in the stables.
你不如过去吃点东西吧
Why don't you get somethin' to eat?
我又不饿
I'm not hungry.
-你肯定饿了  -我要跟你去
-Sure you are. -I wanna come with you.
嘿  听着  我们是来这干正经事的
Hey, listen. We're here to do business. Diplomatically.
我也可以正经啊
Well, I can be diplomatic.
你也可以很饿  对吧
You can be hungry, too, right?
鲍比
Bobby.
-在这等着  -好的
-Wait here. -Okay.
有人坐这吗
Somebody sittin' here?
小托罗
Little Toro.
人一走开  座位就得丢  对吧
Oh, well, you move your feet, you lose your seat, right?
-脑袋也丢了  -说得对
-Lose your head, too. -That's correct.
那小托罗去哪了呢
So, where is Little Toro?
就是你放包的地方
Alllí, where you put him.
-这里  -那里
-Aqui? -Allí.
玩多米诺吧
Let's play some dominoes.
-帕皮可以见你了  -好的
-Papi's ready. -Yeah.
帕皮·格雷科
Papi Greco!
"很有门路"的鲍比
"I-know-a-guy" Bobby.
就是我
That's correct.
快点  鸵鸟  一罐乙醚简直能媲美63年的雪佛兰啊
Quick, an ostrich, a tank of ether, a '63 Impala convertible.
叫它64吧
Make it a '64.
我在我们那边
My side of the border.
我认识个行家
I know a guy.
我说过的吧  他绝不会说不行  不说可能
What did I tell you? He never says no, never says maybe,
也不会说"等着瞧我的本事吧"
never says, "I'll see what I can do."
不错的牛啊
Nice bull.
我希望它是头好种牛
I hope he's a good breeder.
说起小托罗真有点可惜了
That's a shame about Little Toro.
胡里奥发现他揩油
Julio caught him skimming.
噢
Oh.
听起来不像小托罗作风啊
That don't sound like Little Toro.
这是给我的吗  是的
Is that for me? That's correct.
每个人都会揩点油  这是人类天性
Everybody skims a little cream. It's human nature.
人类天性也不能放任
Just 'cause it's human don't mean you let it go.
嗯
Hmm.
线条不错  颜色很好
Nice lines. Good color.
是的
That's right.
确实是行家
He knows a guy.
你准备给我什么呢
What you got for me?
现金
Cash.
Cash?
如果你要给我100,000的话
Supposed to be givin' me 100,000 to deal.
为什么不给我100,000的可卡因呢
Why didn't you give me $100,000 worth of cocaine?
可卡因在哪
Where's the cocaine?
我的买家想要可卡因
My buyer wants cocaine.
那就让他买呗
So let him buy cocaine.
他就是这么打算的  他想买可卡因
That's what he's tryin' to do. He's trying to buy cocaine.
我告诉他我认识卖家  所以我就来找你了
I told him I knew a guy, therefore I come to you.
你就是我认识的卖家  所以我才跟人说了
You the guy I know. That's why I told him.
那把护照拿回去吧
So take back the passports.
在小托罗之后  我们不再接待新的顾客了
After Little Toro, we're not takin' on any new customers.
别这么失礼嘛  我又不是新顾客
Well, no disrespect, but I ain't no new customer.
你跟我打交道很久了
You been dealin' with me for a long time.
你把护照留着吧
You keep the passports.
钱也留着
Keep the money, too.
什么时候你能给我货了  再给我
When you're ready to give me the product, give me the product.
算...
Till then...
你欠我的
You owe me.
这样可不算运动  兄弟们
It's not very sporting, man.
至少要给这些鸡反击的机会吧
At least give the chickens a chance to shoot back.
嘿  兄弟  我说如果让我杀只毫无还手之力的动物
Hey, man, I'm just sayin'. If I'm gonna kill a defenseless animal,
我会把它做成美味的烧烤以尊重它的牺牲
I'm gonna honor its sacrifice by grilling it into some tasty barbecue.
我可不会折磨它
What I'm not gonna do is torture it
来证明我打不到离我小弟弟更远的东西
just to prove I can't hit anything further away than my own pecker.
-你手下可真能吠啊  -是啊
-Your cuate's a real junkyard dog. -Mmm.
你们什么时候认识的
有一晚我给了他点甜头  他就给我回家了
嘿  长得帅的那个牛仔
Hey, cowboy. You, the pretty one.
你有没有听过"你长了张亲娘才会喜欢的脸"
You ever hear the expression, "You got a face only a mother can love"?
这话不适合你  你长得简直连亲娘都看不过眼
That don't apply to you. You are uglier than the devil's asshole itself.
斯蒂格
Stig!
你在干嘛
What are you doin'?
他们在折磨这些鸡  兄弟
They're torturing chickens, man.
你在吃什么
What are you eatin'?
鸡腿
A chicken.
过来  这不一样  明白
Come here. It's not the same thing, okay?
看到桌边那个袋子吗
See that bag over there by the table?
土豆沙拉旁边的自助餐桌
Buffet table next to the potato salad.
看到了  保龄球袋  怎么了
Yeah, the bowling bag. What about it?
小托罗的头在那个袋子里
Little Tom's head is in that bag.
-不是吧  -是的
-Bullshit. -Yeah.
知道吗  这也太过分了  老兄
You know what? That's fucked up, man.
嘿  哇  哇  我们走吧  好吗  快点  走吧
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa. Let's go. Okay? Come on, let's go.
说英语  你这个色鬼
Say it in English, you goat fuck.
来给我吹箫吧
Suck my chicken.
你这么说还真奇怪  肥仔
That's funny comin' from you, fat boy.
你从婴儿起就没见过你的小弟弟吧
You ain't seen your pecker since you were a baby.
不能因为你把手指放到肚脐上
Just 'cause you put your finger in your belly button
有便便流出来  你就觉得那是你的菊花了
and brown shit comes out don't mean it's your asshole.
-你说什么呢  -别担心  兄弟
-What did you say? -Don't worry about it, man.
把它们挖出来  做烧烤吧
Now dig 'em up and make some damn barbecue.
拜拜  娘炮
Bye, chica.
你刚刚跟他抛媚眼了
Did you just wink at him?
我是跟他抛媚眼了  他现在算我的小相好了
I did wink at him, 'cause he's my bitch now.
不是吧
Uh... oh!
-射得好  -谢谢夸奖
-That's good shootin'. -Gracias.
你该知道  小托罗死得不明不白  兄弟
You know, Little Toro never did nothin' to nobody, man.
我们应该去特雷司·克鲁塞斯储贷公司
We should rip off Papi's stash
把帕皮藏起来的钱偷走
at the Tres Cruces Savings and Loan.
帕皮的手下每两周就会把一个
You know, Papi's guy delivers a briefcase
装满钱的公文包送到特雷司·克鲁塞斯去
full of money to Tres Cruces every two weeks.
加起来至少也有300万了吧
That's gotta add up to, what, like three million at least.
如果帕皮知道我们在考虑抢劫特雷司·克鲁塞斯
If Papi knew we were even talkin' about rippin' off Tres Cruces,
土豆沙拉旁边的袋子里装的就是我们的脑袋了
it would be our heads in that bag next to the potato salad.
不可能  那袋子那么小装不下我们俩的脑袋
No way. Our two heads would never fit in a bag that small.
走吧  兄弟  去抢银行吧
Come on, man, let's hit the bank.
小托罗是你的朋友  也是我朋友
Little Toro was your friend. He was my friend.
-那又怎么样呢  -这是什么意思
-So? -What do you mean "so"?
如果是我呢  如果帕皮砍的是我的脑袋呢
What if it was me? What if it was my head Papi ran through the saw mill?
-你不会追杀他  -不会
-You wouldn't come after him? -Nope.
-不会杀了他  -不会
-You wouldn't kill him? -Nope.
该死的  他要是那么对你我会杀了他
Shit, man, he did that to you, I'd kill him.
你知道为什么吗
You know why I'd kill him?
因为我们是一伙的  而且我们有代号
Because you're my people and there's a code.
首先  根本没有代号
There is no code, first of all.
你总是随心所欲  不管付出什么代价
You do whatever you gotta do, whatever it takes.
其次呢
And second?
说得对  我们不是一伙的  你都没同伙
Right, we're not people 'cause you don't have people.
说对了
That's correct.
去墨西哥的目的是什么
Purpose for your visit to Mexico?
捕猎鹌鹑
Quail hunting.
我在图巴市的婶婶心脏病发了  所以我们缩短了行程
My aunt in Tuba City had a heart attack so we cut our trip short.
图巴市
Tuba City?
靠近奥德萨市
It's near Odessa.
好地方
Nice place?
烂地方  但她是我最喜欢的婶婶
Hellhole, but she's my favorite aunt.
-别动  举起手来  -该死
-Don't move. Let me see your hands. -Oh, shit.
-说说你的旅行吧  -我要见律师
-Tell us about your trip. -Lawyer.
-有什么不能说的  -我要见律师
-What's the big deal? -Lawyer.
你去了索诺拉  是不是
You were down in Sonora, weren't you?
你以为杰瑟普探员和禁药取缔机构
You don't think Agent Jessup and the DEA
会不认识你和帕皮·格雷科
know about you and Papi Greco?
律师呢  我要律师
Lawyer. Lawyer.
他们知道你去了他的牧场
They know you were at his ranch.
我只知道我要见律师
I know I need a lawyer.
把帕皮·格雷科的事情跟里斯探员说说
Tell Agent Rees about Papi Greco.
-谁  -帕皮·格雷科
-Who? -Papi Greco.
那是谁  墨西哥圣诞老人还是别的什么
Well, who's that? Some Mexican Santa Claus or something?
别装了  斯蒂格曼先生
Come on, Mr. Stigman.
我觉得跟我们合作对你最有利
I think it's in your best interest to cooperate.
别再玩什么把戏了  行吗
You need to stop playin' the stupid card, all right?
长官  我是很乐意跟你们合作的
Well, ma'am, it's my intent to cooperate with whatever you need.
作为一个美国人  我知道你在履行职责
I mean, as an American, I know you're just doin' your job,
有时候也会错抓像我这样的无辜民众
and sometimes innocent folks like me get caught up in the system.
就像航空公司  他们又不会故意弄丢你的行李  是吧
It's like the airlines. They don't lose your luggage on purpose, right?
但是大家都太自私了
But everybody takes it so damn personal.
够了  斯蒂格曼先生  还想玩把戏吗
Come on, Mr. Stigman. So you wanna play games?
你到底在想什么
Well, what'd you have in mind?
-你想救自己吗  -当然
-Do you wanna help yourself? -Yes.
我真要在他面前这么做吗
Do I have to do it in front of him?
好吧  谈话结束  谢谢  斯蒂格曼先生
All right, we're done here. Thank you, Mr. Stigman.
-你这就走了  -是的
-You gonna leave? -Oh, yes.
哇
Wow.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你跟她在一块怎么能专心工作的  兄弟
How do you concentrate workin' with her, man?
我们说话的功夫里  五名边界探员已经搜查过你的车了
Five border agents are rippin' apart your car as we speak.
他们什么都没找不到
They ain't gonna find anything.
你把可卡因藏在哪里了
Where'd you hide the cocaine?
-外面的人能听到吗  -听不到
-Can they hear us? -No.
-能看到我们吗  -看不到
-Can they see us? -No.
好吧
Okay.
根本就没有可卡因
There was no cocaine.
-你们在当地交易了  -是的
-You had a deal in place. -Right.
五百个护照来交换可卡因
Five hundred passports in return for cocaine.
是的
Right.
嘿  鲍比
Hey, Bobby.
过得好吗  黛比
How you doin', Deb?
很好  兄弟  你的手下斯蒂格是块好料子
Good. Man, your boy Stig's a piece of work.
他朝你抛媚眼了  是不是
He winked at you, didn't he?
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?
鲍比没拿到可卡因
Bobby didn't get the cocaine.
什么  怎么回事
What? What happened?
帕皮给了我现金  我拒绝了
Papi offered me cash. I told him no.
我让他把护照留着
I told him to keep the passports,
最后他肯定会交出可卡因的
so, eventually, he's gotta come up with the cocaine.
那你说可以拉拢的那个人怎么样  小托罗
What about this guy you said you could flip? Little Toro?
我就差一点就说服他了
I got him. It's real close.
我已经不知道你是谁了
I don't know who you are anymore.
就像...
It's like...
你已经脱离了组织
It's like you're out on this limb.
脱离得太远了
And you've been out there way too long.
你到底想说什么
And you're sayin' that to say what?
我可不想去我自己手下的葬礼
I don't like goin' to the funerals of my own men.
那就别来了  头儿  别来了
Well, then don't come, boss. Don't come.
好吗
Okay?
过去的三年里
I spent the last three years of my life
我在墨西哥苟且偷生
crawlin' through a Mexican sewer
一心想要抓到帕皮·格雷科
tryin' to work my way up the line to get next to Papi Greco.
你不能现在把我撤出去
You can't take me off this now.
杰瑟普  他快得手了
Jessup, he's close.
-不能现在把我撤出去  -我明白
-You can't take me off this now. -I know.
现在不行
Not now.
给你两个礼拜的时间
Two weeks.
如果那时候你还没拉拢小托罗  我就把你撤出去
You don't flip Little Toro by then, I'm pullin' ya out.
就这么说定了
We're done.
你觉得杰瑟普知道我们的事吗
Think Jessup knows about us?
"我们"的事  你从不在乎"我们"  不是吗
What "us"? You don't do "us," remember?
哦  好吧
Oh, I remember.
另外  我谈恋爱了
Besides, I'm dating.
好吧  你谈恋爱了...
Oh, right, right. You're dating...
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
你的假想男友  哈维
Your imaginary boyfriend, Harvey.
他不是我男朋友  他也不叫哈维
Uh, he's not my boyfriend, and his name's not Harvey.
我喜欢哈维这个名字  很好听
I like Harvey. It has a nice ring to it. Harvey.
你没资格吃醋  鲍比
You don't get to be jealous anymore, Bobby.
哈维
Harvey.
是你拒绝了我
You pushed me away.
所以你就和哈维在一起了
So you could be with Harvey.
去死吧你
Fuck you.
小托罗死了
Little Toro's dead.
可你告诉杰瑟普你快要拉拢他了
You told Jessup you were close to flipping him.
本来快了
I was.
但当我去农场的时候
But when I got down to the ranch,
我看到帕皮的手下把他的头装在袋子里
Papi's boys was throwin' his head around in a bag.
那也没办法
Well, that's game, then.
没有小托罗接应  杰瑟普会把你撤出去的
With Little Toro off the board, Jessup's pulling you out.
你不说  他就不会知道
Not if you don't tell him.
-我是你的上级  -是的
-I'm your control, Bobby. -That's correct.
我有责任告诉他
I have to tell him.
所以我才需要你
That's why I need you
批准我去抢特雷司·克鲁塞斯储贷银行
to let me rob Tres Cruces Savings and Loan.
你要抢银行
You want to rob a bank?
不  是斯蒂格想要抢银行  是他的主意
No, Stig wants to rob the bank. It's his idea.
我们没有阴谋
So there's no entrapment.
我只是想拿到
What I want is access to that money
帕皮放在保险箱里的钱
that Papi's got in the safe deposit box.
要知道法官可不会批准
You know no judge is gonna give you
你去搜查那些保险箱的
a blanket warrant for the boxes.
不需要搜查令  因为那些钱是赃款
We don't need a warrant. Not if the money's evidence in a crime.
我们只要追查钱的来源
We just trace it back to ownership,
抓到帕皮偷税的证据  就能根据反诈骗法起诉他
we got Papi on tax evasion, possible RICO.
-是吗  -嗯
-Yeah? -Yeah.
那斯蒂格怎么办
And what about Stig?
怎么了
What about him?
他好办
He's a side dish.
当着银行人的面把他抓住
You bust him in front of the bank,
判他20年监禁  就大功告成了
he does a smooth 20 years in the penitentiary, you get a medal.
抢银行能让我们抓到帕皮
The bank gets us Papi.
你要的就是这样  是吧
And that's all that matters, right?
我会不惜一切代价的  宝贝
It takes whatever it takes, baby.
你爱过我吗
Did you ever really love me?
嗯
Hmm?
我很想爱你的
I really meant to love you.
该死
Shit.
门从来不关  你不用敲门
You don't have to knock. It's always open.
好  我们去抢银行吧
Yeah, good. Let's hit the bank.
去抢银行吧
Let's hit the bank.
-特雷司·克鲁塞斯储贷银行  -没错
-The Tres Cruces? -That's correct.
算了吧
Oh, shit.
入境的时候我们为什么被警察带走
Here I am still spinnin' about
我现在还一头雾水呢
how we got yanked outta line at the border.
那你去不去
So you in or you out?
我当然去  只是...
I'm in, yeah. It's just...
你以前遇到过这种事情吗
have you ever had anything like that happen to you before?
他们好像确信我们持有毒品
I mean, they were 100% convinced we were holding.
而且如果帕皮没耍滑头  我们确实会持有毒品
And we would've if Papi hadn't welched on that coke.
你说这些什么意思
So you're sayin' that to say what?
我就是说给你听听
I'm sayin' it's only 'cause you're hearin' it.
不  你肯定有什么意思
No, you sayin' somethin'.
你想跟我说什么
And if you sayin' it, I'm hearin' it 'cause you're sayin' it.
直说出来吧
What are you sayin'? Let it be said.
我觉得你他妈的是在玩我
I think you're fuckin' playin' me.
你想被玩吗
Are you wanna be played?
我跟着你10个月了
I've been at your hip for 10 months,
但出了这事  我觉得你可能是在玩我
but after this, I think maybe you're playin' me.
-你上当了  -不  我没有
-I got you. -No, you didn't.
你有  你眼角抽动了
Oh, I did. The corner of your eye was twitchin'.
眼角  我的眼角没抽动
The corner? That wasn't a twitch.
-那是抛媚眼  -那是我的招牌动作
-That was a wink. -That's my move.
那是帕皮胖得像圆球的儿子
Yup, that's Papi's chubby little kid right there.
整天吃油炸玉米粉饼...
Feed that motherfucker quesadillas...
天啊
Oh, my God.
她也很圆
She's chubby, too.
但圆的很是地方
In all the right places.
凭什么那个糟老头能娶到这样的美人
How does an old, fat, ugly fuck get a girl like that?
因为有钞票
Money.
好了  他来了
All right, here we go.
每隔两周
Same thing every two weeks.
帕皮都会带着一箱现金  乘飞机穿过边境
Papi flies over the border with a briefcase full of cash.
然后他陪妻子一周
He spends a week with the mistress.
费雷·诺斯·胡里奥把钱
Ferret Nose Julio drives it out
送到特雷司·克鲁塞斯储贷银行
to the Tres Cruces Savings and Loan.
现在有三百万了吧
Think they got three million in the bank, huh?
真是轻松
Easy.
来了
Bingo.
都是钱啊  都是钱啊
Money, money, money, money.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
你去餐馆点个甜甜圈怎么样
Why don't you hit the diner and check out the doughnuts?
说实话  我更想吃熏牛肉配土豆泥
I'm kinda more in a corned beef hash mood, to tell you the truth.
你没听过那句老话吗
You never heard the saying,
"永远不要抢三郡最佳
"Never rob a bank across from a diner
甜甜圈饭店对面的银行"
that has the best doughnuts in three counties"?
-没有这句老话  -有
-That's not a saying. -Yes, it is.
-这是你说的  不是什么老话  -你没听过吗
-I get what you're sayin', but it's not a saying. -You never heard it?
这现在是句老话了
It is a saying. It's a saying now.
好吧  不跟你废话了
Okay. Let you tell it.
行动吧
Make the move.
缉毒局不良探员
Bad DEA agent.
-我坏吗  -是的
-Am I bad? -Yes, you are.
我是个坏女孩
I'm a bad girl?
是的
Yes, you are.
斯蒂格决定明天3:00去抢劫银行
Stig decided to hit the bank tomorrow, 3:00.
斯蒂格决定
Stig decided?
无论我去不去  他都会去
Well, with or without me, he's goin' in.
我还没向杰瑟普报告
Well, I still haven't talked to Jessup.
斯蒂格不知道这个  明天三点他要行动了
Stig doesn't know that. 3:00 tomorrow he's goin' in.
如果我们想抓到帕皮  我得和他一起去
If we want Papi, I gotta go in with him.
你让我别无选择  不是吗
You're not even gonna give me a choice, are you?
我不让你选择是在保护你
I'm givin' you no other options as a way to protect you.
你去通知警方  明天3:05银行门口等着我们
Just have the troops meet me outside the bank, 3:05 when we come out.
3:05  是吗
3:05.
别朝我开枪
Okay. And don't shoot me.
-你看着办吧  -那我看看
-Even if you want to. -We'll see.
请出示证件  小伙子
License and registration, cowboy.
好样的
Cute.
-怎么了  提莫  -怎么了  哥们
-What's up, Teemo? -What's up, brother?
-还好吗  哥们  我很想你  -我也想你
-How are you, brother? I miss you, man. -I miss you, man.
给你留了一个火鸡汉堡  加了酱汁
Got you a turkey burger. Special sauce.
指挥官想见你
Commander wants to see you.
好的
Yes, sir.
快要成功了
So, half a mile from home.
鲍比已经跃跃欲试了
I got Bobby all wound up and ready to go, sir.
这是你申请的武器
Ordnance you requested.
知道吗  上将对你的表现很满意
Do you know, the Admiral's proud of what you've done.
离成功之差一步之遥
You've gone way out on a limb.
如果明天银行的计划成功
If the bank falls right tomorrow,
他答应把你调回来  重新回到队伍里
he says you can come in from the cold, rejoin your brothers.
太好了  能再穿上军装我就知足了
Great. Be good just to put the uniform back on, sir.
我参军可不是为了和毒贩一起违法乱纪的
I didn't join the Navy to commit felonies and hang with drug dealers.
你可是个出色的罪犯
Even if you're damn good at it?
我只是服从命令
I do what I do for the Navy, sir.
这些都是上将的计划
It's all part of the Admiral's plan.
我们把这三百万从银行里取出来
We get this three million from the bank,
就能采取跨界行动  捣毁帕皮他们的窝点
we run cross-border ops on Papi and all the other cartels.
所以明天的目标只有一个
So tomorrow, clean and precise.
就是拿走保险箱里所有的钱  一分不剩  明白吗
Tick all the boxes, nothing left undone. You got it?
明白
Yes, sir.
出发
Let's go.
嘿  夹克不错
Hey, nice jacket.
嘿  告诉你母亲一声
Hey, tell your mother she's gotta move out
她得从我的房子里搬出去了
of my house at some point, man.
你要哪个头套  小丑还是怪物
All right, what do you want, clown or Frankie?
怪物
Frankie.
你用那22块干什么了
So, what'd you do with the 22?
我从我表哥那里买了台咖啡机
Traded to my cousin for an espresso machine.
那你需要特制的咖啡豆  是吧
You're gonna need special beans for that, right?
停  停
Uh, uh, uh.
你可以掏手枪  不过你可要想好了
You can reach for your firearm, but do it real slow.
这楼里还有其他人吗
Any other people in the buildin'?
-这是怎么回事  -抢银行
-What the hell is this? -It's a bank robbery.
只是先把你们关起来
Only instead of robbin' the bank
这样过一会儿
and lettin' you chase after us,
你们就不用追着我们傻跑了
we decided to come after you first.
走吧
Let's go.
警察局
把枪交给我
All right, give me your gun, there.
所有人都坐下  坐在地上
All right, everybody sit down. Everybody sit down on the floor.
柜台后面的女士  把手举起来  不要放在警报器上
Ladies behind the counter, keep your hands visible, not on the alarms.
快走  快走
Let's go, let's go!
别怕  姑娘们  把抽屉里所有的钱都给他们
It's all right, girls. Just give 'em the drawer cash.
我们说要抽屉里的钱了吗
Did we ask for the drawer cash?
快点  坐下  坐下
Come on, come on, come on. Sit right here. Sit, sit.
坐在地上
Let's go, on the floor.
-嘿  小心那个保安  -嘿  嘿
-Hey, guard! -Hey! Hey.
不要敬酒不吃  好吗
Look, I'm tryin' to be polite, all right?
好好坐着  一会就好了
Just sit tight and this'll be over soon.
打开门
Open the gate.
我没有钥匙
I don't have a key.
你说什么
What'd you say?
好了
Easy.
如果你再骗我一次  你就要倒霉了
You lie to me again, it's gonna be more than a fuckin' problem.
滚过去
Get out there, now.
在地上坐好
Get on the floor.
准备好了吗  我进去了
You good? I'm goin' in.
嘘  没事的
Shh. It's all right.
哦  蒂莫西
Oh, Timothy.
嘿  别怕
Hey, it's okay.
别怕  嗯
It's okay. Yeah?
好了  给你
Okay. Here you go.
烟火表演马上开始
Showtime! Fire in the hole!
糟糕
Holy shit!
嘿  怪物  有点不对劲
Hey, Frankie, somethin's not right.
所有的箱子都装满现金
They're all stuffed with money.
你说过只有一两箱现金的
I thought you said there would only be one or two.
每个里面都是现金
Every single one of them.
一共有32个保险箱
I'm at 32 boxes and counting.
肯定不止三百万
Look, there's way more than 3 million.
这里还有很多
And there's still a lot more here.
好吧  全带走  以后再数
All right, well, take 'em all. We'll figure it out later.
你先走  我去搬剩下的
You go ahead, I'll get the rest.
好吧
All right.
听着
Listen.
等会外面可能会有枪响
May be gunfire outside, okay? So if it hits,
你带着大家躲到柜台后面
you get everybody behind the counters.
这是对面警察局牢房的钥匙
This is for the jail across the street.
你去把那里的警察放出来
You let the cops out. Let'em out.
快点
Come on.
这是可远远不止三百万美元
That is a hell of a lot more than $3 million.
你数了有多少了吗
How much, you figure?
我们今天难道是走了狗屎运
We couldn't be the luckiest chumps on the face of the earth, could we?
-你觉得幸运  -不
-You feel lucky? -No, I don't.
这不是帕皮的钱
I mean, this can't be Papi's money.
拿了这些钱  他们肯定会追着我们不放
People are gonna chase us off the end of the earth for money like this.
不好意思  斯蒂格  但我有个不幸的消息...
Well, I hate to tell you this, Stig, but I got more bad news...
把手慢慢地从背后拿出来  鲍比
You take that hand away nice and slow, Bobby.
好了
Okay.
把枪放下  斯蒂格
Put the gun down, Stig.
知道吗  我很喜欢你
You know I really like you, right?
我也很喜欢你
I like you, too.
-不  你不喜欢我  -我喜欢你
-No, you don't. -Yes, I do.
没人喜欢我  而且我习惯了
Nobody likes me, okay? And I'm okay with it.
我喜欢你  你比其他人都好
I do. I like you more than most.
是因为我拿着枪指着你  你才这么说的吗
You're not just sayin' it 'cause I got a gun pointed to you?
为什么不把枪放下来呢
Why don't you just put the gun down?
该死
Shit.
哦
Oh.
没搞错吧
Hot-doggin'!
抱歉了  哥们
I'm sorry, man.
你为什么要这么做
What'd you do that for?
-我不得不这么做  -不可能
-Shit, man, I had to! -No, you didn't.
就是一点皮肉伤  没事的
It's just a little flesh wound. You'll be all right.
喝点药  你就没事了...
Drink the water, and then you'll be able...
那是什么
What is that?
你手里拿的是警徽吗
In your hand. Is that a badge in your hand?
别他妈告诉我  你是个内鬼
Tell me you're not a no-good, two-timin' son of a bitch.
内鬼
Two-timin'?
-快说  -是你开枪打了我
-Tell me. -You shot me.
等一下  等一下
Hey, wait a minute. Wait a minute, man. Hang on.
别走
No, you wait a minute.
斯蒂格
Stig.
嘿
Hey.
美国是世界上最伟大的国家
The United States is the greatest country in the world
因为我们可以接受人们
because we accept a man is, at his core,
贪婪
greedy,
自私
selfish
的本性
and covetous.
我没办法  他们抢走了钥匙
I had no choice. They took my key.
我不是心甘情愿地打开金库门的
I would never willingly open the vault.
把手放在桌子上
Keep your hands on the desk, please.
在美国人人平等
In America, we line everybody up.
所以  "人定胜天"
Say, "You're on your own."
"抓住一切机会"
"Grab all you can grab."
我是无辜的
I'm innocent.
没有人是无辜的
Nobody's innocent, friend.
这世间只有罪恶
There's just the guilty,
和狂妄
the ignorant
还有不幸
and the unlucky.
是不是你拿了我的钱
Did you take our money?
你们看来就像等车一样悠哉
You fellas look like you're waitin' for a bus.
你完事了告诉我们一声
You guys let us know when you're done.
我完事了  谢谢你们配合
Oh, I'm done, and thank you for the courtesy.
他是谁
Who is that guy?
你听说过上帝魔手吗
You heard of the hidden hand of God?
那家伙就是
Well, that's God's son of a bitch.
打电话给DDO  查出哪些人知道我们放了钱在这儿
Call the DDO and get a list of everyone who knew we had money in this bank.
你俩不觉得戴上墨镜很白痴吗
You two realize those sunglasses make you look like assholes.
打扰下  那家餐馆啥时候爆炸的
Excuse me, when'd that diner burn?
昨天
Yesterday.
我要见餐馆服务员
I want interviews with the wait staff
和所有在场的客人
and every customer in the place.
只是机油引起火灾而已
It was just a grease fire.
我有问你吗  高莫
Did I ask your opinion, Gomer?
你有听说过
You ever hear the saying,
"永远不要抢三郡最佳
"Never rob a bank across from a diner
甜甜圈饭店对面的银行"
with the best doughnuts in three counties"?
如果那家餐馆火灾纯属巧合
If that diner fire's a coincidence,
那是因为我们一直看得不够严
it's only 'cause we ain't looking hard enough.
那可是好大一笔钱
That is an impressive amount of greenbacks.
4312.5万美金  长官
43,125,000 of 'em, sir.
好
Mmm.
重新数下  装起来  我们藏到库里面
Recount it. Pack it up. We'll stow it back in Corpus.
我印象中应该从那银行拿到
It was my impression we were supposed to come out of that bank
最多300万美金  长官
with 3 million at most, sir.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
这些钱是谁的
Whose money was it?
坏人不值得拥有
Bad men unworthy of it.
你知道鲍比·宾斯是缉毒局的吗
Did you know Bobby Beans was DEA?
不知道
No, I didn't.
无意冒犯  你的表情不够惊讶
No offense, sir, but you really need to work on your surprised face.
如果他是缉毒局的  却帮你打劫银行
Well, if he was DEA, he helped you rob a bank.
非正义所为  我决不饶恕银行劫匪
Which means he's dirty, and for that, I have no mercy.
-你把他丢在哪了  -沙漠
-Where'd you leave him? -In the desert.
-他死了吗  -差不多
-Is he dead? -More than likely.
"差不多"
"More than likely."
你知道这意味着什么吗
You wanna tell me what that means?
让你和鲍比·宾斯合作就是为了
The whole point of you working with Bobby Beans
灭掉他  斩草除根
was to kill him off and create a cut-out
监管所就查不到我们头上来了
so the OP couldn't get traced back to us.
我掩饰得天衣无缝  我们不会被查到的
My cover's solid. There's no way it'll trace back.
我掩饰得天衣无缝  我们不会被查到的  长官
My cover is solid. There's no way it'll trace back, sir.
这里轮得到你做决定吗
That's a call made above your pay grade.
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
派两个人把钱藏到海军基地
Assign two of the boys to stow the money back at the naval base.
其他人跟我们去找宾斯的尸体
The rest'll come with us to check on the body of Mr. Beans.
斯蒂格曼  要一起来吗
Stigman, wanna come with me?
-你好啊  伙计  -你好
-Hey there, buddy. -Hey.
你是墨西哥的吗
You habla?
是  是
Yeah, yeah.
我是
I hablo.
好  那就好
Good, that's good.
没看到证件前  别信他
Don't trust in him till you see his paper.
如果他有证件  我会看的  你有  对吧
If he's got papers, I'll see his papers. You got papers, right?
不  不  我没证件
No. No, I got no papers.
那就麻烦了
Well, that's gonna be a problem.
瘦杰和我自愿来这
See, Slim Jay and me, we done assigned ourselves
保护边境
protection this here stretch of the border.
既是执行公务  也是个人意愿
Officially unofficially.
所以我们必须检查你的证件
So we really gonna have to see your papers.
确认你是不是穆斯林啥的
Make sure you ain't no Muslim or nothin'.
是吧  有  我有证件的
Oh, yeah. No, I do have it.
拿你的枪过来
And let me have your gun.
给我
Give it to me.
谢谢
Gracias.
你知道怎么祈祷吧
You know how to pray?
提莫  进展怎样啦  伙计们
Teemo. How we doin', boys?
有看到鲍比·宾斯吗
Any sign of Bobby Beans?
查遍了东南片区
Checked all the washes to the southeast.
没发现尸体
No sign of a body.
好吧
All right.
斯蒂格  你让我们大失所望
Well, Stig, you put us in quite a hole.
我不这样认为  长官  您才是指挥官
I don't see it that way, sir, but you're the man with the oak leaves.
你曾经让我引以为豪
All that pride I had in you.
对我忠心耿耿
That loyalty?
现在你不再值得信任
You just tossed it to the wind
是的  长官  抱歉
Yes, sir. I'm sorry, sir.
该死的
God damn it.
他不见了
He's in the wash!
快  快  快
Go, go, go!
快把他找出来
Come on, let's flush him out!
你去哪儿  斯蒂格曼
Where you going, Stigman?
逃跑也没用
It doesn't matter if you run.
你被通缉了  现在你是刺伤宪兵后在逃6个月的逃兵
Your jacket's wired, so you're six-months AWOL after stabbing an MP.
无论你联系谁  他们都会
You talk to anyone, they're just gonna
把你交回给我处置
hand you right back over to me.
你没事吧
You all right?
-没事  -那就他妈的赶快起来
-Yeah. -Then get your ass up!
扔掉枪
Toss the gun.
他妈的
Fuck!
快
Move!
赶快  赶快
Come on, come on!
该死
Damn it!
天啊  我该怎么弄啊
Jesus! What am I supposed to do with this?
天啊
Aw, man. Aw!
不是吧
Come on.
我是个兽医  不是外科医生
I'm a vet, not a trauma surgeon.
我帮不了你了  你走吧
I can't help you with this, man. You gotta go.
走去哪
Go where?
你离开吧  我帮不了
You gotta leave. I can't do anything.
肯尼  你记得几个月之前
Kenny, you remember a couple of months ago
说要卖500支氯胺酮给我吗
you offered to sell me 500 hits of ketamine?
记得  你说没兴趣
Yeah, you said you weren't interested.
对
Right.
因为我是缉毒局探员
'Cause I'm a DEA agent.
如果你不治好我
And if you don't fix me up,
我就去药管局
I'm gonna go to the D.A.,
告诉他们你喜欢在多莉·艾莫丝的演唱会上游荡
I'm gonna tell them that you like cruising Tori Amos concerts,
卖K粉给那些眼泪汪汪的小女生
selling Special K to little weepy college girls.
你不可能是警察
There's no way you're a cop.
-不可能  -对
-No? -No.
-你确定吗  -我确定
-You sure? -I'm positive.
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
也有权让律师陪审
You have the right to have a lawyer present during questioning.
还要我继续下去吗
Do I need to keep going?
不  我信了  你是警察
No, I'm good. You're a cop.
好  很好
Okay. Okay.
衣服不错
Nice shirt.
谢谢  是杰西潘尼家的[美国零售巨头]
Thanks. It's JCPenney's.
-是吗  -是
-Yeah? -Yeah.
好  等一下
All right, hold on one second.
最新电影大片首发 请访问
新气息论坛 www.xinqixi.com
欢迎光临卡米诺瑞尔酒店
Welcome to the Camino Real.
谢谢
Thank you.
喂
Hey.
-你昨天迟到了  -天啊
-You were late. -Jesus Christ.
到底发生什么事了
What the hell happened?
-不好意思  -不好意思  让下
-Excuse us. -Excuse me.
我打劫银行了啊  你呢
I robbed a bank. What happened to you?
我和6个探员3:05到达那里
I was there with six agents at 3:05.
-不  你没有  -我有
-No, you weren't. -Yes, I was.
你迟到了
You were late.
是你早离开了
You went early.
看来你并没适时亮出警徽
And it's not as if you couldn't have
阻止他抢劫
pulled your badge at any time and stopped it.
-我阻止了  但斯蒂格射了我一枪  -什么
-I did. Stig shot me. -What?
我肩膀中枪了
He shot me in the shoulder.
我们得带你去医院
We gotta take you to the hospital.
然后打断你和哈维的约会  我可不想这样
And interrupt your rendezvous with Harvey? I don't think so.
我们现在必须做的是
This is what we need to do,
找到斯蒂格和钱
we need to find Stig, we need to find the money.
好  听着
All right. Listen.
先让我上楼找编个借口离开
Let me go upstairs, make my excuses,
然后我们一起去找斯蒂格  好吗
and then we'll find Stig together, okay?
好  我们这样吧  这样
Okay, let's do this. Let's do this.
你再查下斯蒂格的底
Why don't you recheck Stig's background?
可能我们漏掉了什么  好吗
Maybe there was something that we missed. All right?
我现在去斯蒂格家  看下能找到什么
I'm going to Stig's apartment and see what I can find out.
-好吗  -好
-All right? -Okay.
代我向哈维问好
Tell Harvey I said hi.
你帮谁包扎伤口了
Who'd you patch up?
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我在说什么
What am I talkin' about?
外面停着辆沙地车
Well, there's a dune buggy parked out back
是一个中枪的人偷的
that was stolen by a man with a bullet hole in him.
在他中枪前
Now, before he had a bullet hole in him,
他炸了一个饭店  打劫了银行
he burned down a diner and robbed a bank.
我什么都不知道  所以...
I don't know anything about that, so...
好吧
Okay.
好
Okay?
很好
Fair enough.
我这样问你吧
Say, let me ask you somethin'.
你有玩过俄罗斯轮盘赌吗
You ever play Russian roulette?
当然没有  我在想什么呢
'Course not. What am I thinkin'?
主要是  大多数人
The thing is, most people,
都把枪放在太阳穴上
they put the gun to the temple.
嗯  那太笨了
And that's, well, that's just stupid.
假如
What if...
子弹在第一膛怎么办呢
The bullet's in the first chamber?
你在人家还有机会告诉你想知道的事之前
You blow a man's head off 'fore he's had a chance
就让人家脑袋开花了
to tell you what you want to know.
不  不  不  不要啊
No. No, no. Come on, man.
多好的例子
Case in point.
斯蒂格
Stig!
Stig.
接电话  鲍比
Pick up, Bobby.
你他妈的来这干嘛啊  鲍比
What the fuck are you doing here, Bobby?
你躲个屁啊
What're you duckin' for, man?
你知道我在算计你  对吧
You know I set you up, right?
他们告诉我你的底了
They told me all about you.
很难对付  交游广阔  没有亲人
Tough cat. Knows everybody. Doesn't have people.
这样的人最适合清除
That guy? Well, shit, that guy's a perfect cut-out.
要是给他一枪  也没人会在乎的  对吧
I mean, he takes a bullet, who's gonna care, right?
接电话
Pick up the phone.
接那个破电话  鲍比
Pick up the damn phone, Bobby.
你有话要说吗
You got anything to say?
第一个问题
First question,
如果你是缉毒局的  清白的  为什么一个人来
if you're DEA and you're clean, why are you here alone?
你的幕后黑手是谁  鲍比
Where's your backup, Bobby?
你这种态度
Come on, it's this kind of attitude
让我觉得你不是好人
makes me think you're not one of the good guys.
如果我想的话  在你进入
If I wanted you, I could've had you
那栋楼之前就可以把你毙了  鲍比
before you walked into that building, Bobby.
好酷的枪  斯蒂格
That's a beautiful rifle, Stig.
是部队的吗
Is that Army issue?
凯马特是美国最大的折扣零售商
你喜欢吗  不  从凯马特买回来的  特价
You like that? No, it's Kmart. Blue Light Special.
现在回答我  你的幕后指使者是谁
Now answer my question. Where's your backup?
不  不  那是军用枪
No, no, that's a military rifle.
军队为什么要打劫银行  斯蒂格
What's the military doing robbing banks, Stig?
我们可以坦诚相待吗  鲍比
Can we just have a straight-up conversation, Bobby?
我让你右脑袋开花吧
I got you dead to rights.
是吗  那射我吧
Yeah? So shoot me.
第二次了
Again.
不射吗
No?
那我来吧
I'll shoot myself.
哈  手法不错嘛
Huh. Not bad.
谢谢欣赏
I'm glad you're impressed.
你在试我会不会先开枪  对吗
Were you testing me to see if I would shoot first?
钱在哪里  斯蒂格
Where's the money, Stig?
如果你是清白的  也许可以告诉你  但你不是
If I thought you were clean, I might tell you, but I don't, so I can't.
你说谎  钱不在你这  对吧  到底在哪里
You're lying. You don't have it, do you? Where's the money?
-噢  不是吧  -怎么了
-Oh, shit. -What?
原来不只有你
You're not the only one I was expecting.
三个恶心的人刚出现了
Three very nasty men just showed up.
如果在我家发现你  后果就严重了
If they find you in my place, they will get ugly.
他们是谁
Who are they?
昨天我还说  和他们是一家人
Yesterday I'd have said they were my family.
今天他们就要来杀我了
Today they kinda wanna kill me.
-我明白你的感受  -去你的
-I understand the feeling. -You know, fuck you.
你知道什么是家吗  你连家人都没有
What do you know about family? You don't even have people.
不  鲍比  别走那
No, Bobby, that's a stupid idea.
他们已经上楼了
They're already comin' up the stairs.
鲍比
Bobby!
跟你说过了  现在这样  鲍比
I told you. Now, Bobby,
把扬声器关了  接你的手机  好吗
hang up the speaker and answer your cell phone, okay?
如果要我帮忙的话...
If you want me to help you out...
说
Yeah.
先呆在阴影处  好吗
Just stay in the shadows, okay?
我会引导你逃出来
I'm gonna guide you out from there.
等下
Wait.
他在你后面  你最好冲过大厅吧
He's comin' up your rear. You better dart across the hall.
去卧室  躲在柜后面
Go over to the bedroom and hide behind the lockers.
快
Go.
好  鲍比  你冲过去大厅  快
All right, Bobby, you're gonna wanna scoot across the hall. Go.
鲍比
Bobby, Bob...
他妈的
Shit.
-提莫  -屋顶
-Teemo! -Rooftop!
目标在移动
Target's on the move!
抱歉  提莫
Sorry, Teemo.
我们的钱在哪
Where's our money?
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talkin' about.
你觉得缉毒局冲进我们银行
You think DEA can just waltz into our bank,
偷走我们的钱  我们不会反抗吗
steal our money, and we're not gonna kick?
你的伙计鲍比·特伦奇偷了我们4300万美金
Your man Bobby Trench stole 43 million of our dollars.
我们想要回来
We'd like it back.
因为本来就是我们的
Because it's our money.
因为这大逆不道啊
Because it's a blatant act of disrespect.
因为钱是我们的
And because it's our money.
你终于打来了  鲍比
Please tell me it's you, Bobby.
有斯蒂格的新资料吗
Anything new on Stig?
我找到的所有资料都显示他是清白的
He's comin' up clean on every database I'm cleared for.
没有军方关系吗  没有服役记录
No military connection? No record of service?
要更深入调查  要得到杰瑟普的授权
To go deeper, I'd need to get clearance from Jessup.
试下找你在军队的老同事吧
Well, try your old contacts in the military.
我要把知道的一切都告诉杰瑟普
I'm gonna tell Jessup everything I know.
等下  你确定吗
Wait, are you sure?
肯定会有人知道银行的钱是谁的
Someone has to know whose money was in the bank.
有啊  斯蒂格
Yeah. Stig.
斯蒂格连我是缉毒局的都不知道
Stig didn't even know I was DEA.
而且也有人在追杀他
Besides, somebody tried to kill him, too.
鲍比  让我帮你  你需要什么
Bobby, let me help you. What do you need?
别着急  再见
Take it easy. Bye.
鲍比
Bobby.
去你的
Fuck!
连一个人都拿不下  关门
That's how you take down a man. Now shut the door.
死就死吧
Just let it come.
罗伯特·林恩·特伦奇探员
Agent Robert Lynn Trench.
也叫鲍比·T  鲍比·B  鲍比·宾斯
A.k.a. Bobby T, a.k.a. Bobby B, a.k.a. Bobby Beans.
我们来聊聊吧
Let's have a chat.
你偷了4312.5万美金
You stole $43.125 million
这不属于你的
that did not belong to you.
实话实说
Now, man-to-man,
缉毒局里面谁指使你打劫我们银行的
who at DEA authorized you to rob our bank?
你是银行家吗
You a banker?
你玩过俄罗斯轮盘赌吗
You ever play Russian roulette?
主要是
Thing is,
大多数人都把枪放在太阳穴上
most people put the gun to the temple.
那简直蠢到家了
Well, that's just stupid.
你在人家还有机会告诉你想知道的事之前
You blow a man's head off 'fore he's had a chance
就把别人打死了
to tell you what you wanna know.
还弄的自己一身脏
Mess up your suit, too.
谁借你豹子胆来偷我们的钱的
Who told you it was all right to take our money?
"你们的钱  你们的银行"
"Our money. Our bank."
你谁啊
Who are ya?
你如果不知道我是谁
If you don't know who I am,
你怎么把4千3百万钱给偷走的
how did you know to steal our 43 million?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talkin' about.
-你不知道  -的确不知道
-You don't? -No.
这样啊...
Well...
那钱哪儿去了
Where's the money?
我的天啊
Oh, boy.
说实话...
Well, uh...
我可以担保  钱肯定不在这下面
it ain't down there, I can guarantee you that.
哇哦  哇哦
Whoo-hoo.
不愧外号  鲍比·蛋蛋
A.k.a. Bobby Balls.
干净利落  妥妥的
Clean and shaven.
你知道  你算什么吗
You know what you are?
你
You
就是个变节的缉毒局条子
are a dirty DEA agent.
没错
That's right.
你就是个抢银行  杀上司的
You're a dirty DEA agent who robbed a bank.
变节缉毒局条子
And shot your boss.
不管你到哪个政府部门申诉
You walk into any federal office,
你都会得到这个结果
and that's the story they're gonna have.
要不然你就给我4312.5万美刀
Unless you bring me $43.125 million,
那你无债走人  轻松
and you walk away. Clean.
我跟你说清楚  讲明白了吗
Have I properly incentivized you?
不能再明白了
More than you know.
除非你想老死在监狱里  不然的话你最好搞定这事情
Unless you wanna rot in jail, you best get after it.
去吧  快去吧
Go on, now. Go on.
好吧
All right.
你觉得  他不是罪有应得吗
You're thinkin' he deserved better?
你没感觉错
You're right.
嘿  鲁迪
Hey, Rudy.
好啊  哈维尔
Hola, Javier.
早啊  帕皮
Morning, Papi.
别乱动
Don't move.
快进去
Go inside, quick.
老妈
Mommy!
我们偷的钱  到底是谁的
Whose money did we steal?
你真想知道
You really wanna know?
我真想知道
I really wanna know.
别乱来  老家伙  进去  给我进去
Easy, old man, get in there. Get in there.
我到时候报复死你
Payback's a bitch!
报复死你啊
哦  哦  哦
Uh, uh, uh.
-哇哦  鲍比  -把枪放下  把钥匙给我
-Whoa, Bobby. -Drop the gun. Give me the keys.
把钥匙给我  慢慢的来
Give me the keys. Nice and easy.
我做不到
I can't do that.
-为什么  -我先抓到他的  先下手为强
-Why not? -Well, I got him first. I got dibs.
我还抓这点44呢  帕皮我提走了  把钥匙给我
I got a .44. I'm taking Papi. Give me the keys.
你要钥匙  你自己来拿
You want 'em? Come get 'em.
我看到那眼珠骨溜溜的转起来了
Now, I see the wheels turnin'.
你在想要不用蒙眼布  也许用牙齿好一点
You're thinkin' a little blindfold, maybe use your teeth.
我没想这东西  你知道我在想什么吗
That's not what I'm thinkin'. You know what I'm thinkin'?
我了个草  伙计  这算什么
Oh, shit, man. How's that?
打脸都不打声招呼
That was uncalled for.
操  我还是喜欢那个"很有门路"的鲍比
Shit. I liked you better when you were "I-know-a-guy" Bobby.
那个鲍比还是个好人
That Bobby was a good guy.
我喜欢没事对女服务员眉来眼去
Well, I liked you better when you were winkin' at waitresses
枪扫鸡头的你
and shootin' the heads off of chickens.
把钥匙给我  把钥匙给我
Give me the keys. Give me the keys.
我操
Shit!
-你还会开枪的  -没错  把钥匙给我
-You saw that move comin'? -That's correct. Give me the keys.
见了个鬼了  你还真倔啊
Damn, you're good.
反正总要有人弯腰捡钥匙的
Now, one of us is gonna have to pick up those keys.
-你猜啊  -好吧  我去捡  行了吧
-Guess. -All right. I'll get 'em, all right?
-捡起来  捡起来  -把钱移开点  伙计
-Get 'em, get 'em. -Put that musket away, man.
-嘿  停下来  -停下来
-Hey, pull over! -Pull over?
嘿  帕皮  你觉得我开车爽吗
Hey, Papi, you like my drivin'?
我操
Oh, shit!
你来啊  鲍比  我可没空整天陪你的啊
Come on, Bobby, I ain't got all damn day!
你到底想干什么
What do you wanna do?
哦
Ow!
够了  够了  够了  放开我
All right. All right, all right. All right, let me go.
你先放开我
You let me go first.
不行  你放开我
No, you let me go.
数三下  一起放
On three. On three.
一  二  三
One. Two. Three.
看到没  你现在给我不相信你的理由了
See? Now you're making me not be able to trust you.
说话算话  数三下  我们都放手
On the count of three, we'll let each other go.
-好吗  -好吧  互不吃亏
-All right? -All right. That's fair.
一  二
One. Two.
三
Three.
我就知道  放开我
I knew it. Let me go.
-不放  -那我放开你  我放你
-No! -I'm gonna let you go. I'm gonna let you go.
-好的  -一...
-All right. -One...
哦
Ow!
老实说  伙计  你不得不承认这样够尽兴  对吧
Come on, man. You gotta admit, that was kind of fun, no?
你不喜欢啊
You didn't like that?
你到底是谁啊
Who are you?
见鬼
Shit.
-美国海军情报员  -是吗
-U.S. Navy Intel. -Yeah?
起码我以前是
Or I was.
我的上级制造假象
My commander FUBARed my jacket.
说我捅了个宪兵后擅自失踪了
And now I'm AWOL after stabbing an MP.
你还算好的呢  他们诬陷我杀害上司
You're lucky. They got me framed for killing my boss.
那你上司派你最要好的四个朋友来干掉你吗
Did your boss order your four closest friends to kill you?
没有  算你的狠
No, you got me there.
海军士官迈克尔·斯蒂格曼
Petty Officer Michael Stigman.
缉毒局探员鲍比·特伦奇  但我猜你早就知道了
DEA Officer Bobby Trench, but I guess you know that already.
荣幸荣幸
Pleasure.
那怎么说呢  是你碰巧遇上我的
So, what, you just happened to pick me,
还是上头派你来故意跟我对着干的
or you got orders to set me up on purpose?
我有命在身啊  伙计  我也不知道你是缉毒局的人
I had orders, man. I didn't know you were DEA.
我的人知道  但他们情报局的
My people did. But they're Intel.
他们也不知道多少情况
There's not much they don't know.
你的人
Your people?
我现在就想把事情搞清楚
Now I'm just trying to piece together the truth,
到时候越过我长官  直接跟海军司令汇报
so I can take it over my commander's head to the Admiral.
所以他们才想干掉我  所以我才想跟帕皮说清楚
That's why they wanna kill me and why I wanted to talk to Papi.
好吧
Right.
这样的话...
Well...
我觉得  我们可以一起去问他个清楚
I guess we can both talk to him at the same time.
什么  我们现在变搭档了
What, like we're workin' together?
不是  我们才不是什么搭档
No, not like we're working together.
-那才像话  -不是  我们只是有交叉而已
-Yeah. -No, like we're workin' in the same vicinity.
-就是一起  -调查的地方一样
-Together. -In the same area code.
-那就是一起  -同一个郡而已
-Together. -The same county.
别拿"四海一家"套我身上啊
And don't get all "We Are The World" on me either.
等这事完了  我要开枪还是会开枪的
When this is over, I'm still gonna shoot you.
但我们现在是搭档啦
But we're partners.
拜托  伙计  黑键白键不分开的
Come on, man, Ebony and Ivory.
见鬼  我觉得他吐死了  反正不是吐了就是死了
Shit, I think he puked. He's puked or he's dead.
哦没错  他吐了
Oh, yeah, he puked.
嘿
Hey.
我他妈到时候整死你们两个小崽子
I'm gonna fuckin' kill you both.
看样子要点时间啊
This might take a while.
伙计  我有时候陪你耗着
I got all day, partner.
等等
Hold on.
我送个香屁给你  妥妥的收下啊
Let me put that in there with ya. Put that on ya.
-那...-搭档  你打算怎么来
-So... -Partner, how you wanna do this?
这话中听  特别是从你嘴里说出来
I like that, it's got a nice roll off your tongue there.
我们还没这么熟  别说得这么亲  保持距离
We're not that close. Don't kumbaya with me. Don't kumbaya.
我去拿水桶和毛巾  我们给这混蛋上上水刑
I'm gonna get my bucket and towel and waterboard his ass.
不了  我们给他个机会说清楚  你有什么要说的吗
No, we gotta give him a chance to talk. You got anything to say?
但愿你们喜欢卵蛋的味道
I hope you guys like the taste of balls,
因为到时候我会把它们割下来  塞进你们嘴里
because I'm gonna chop yours off, stuff 'em in your mouths.
看到没有
See?
也许到时候我换着塞
Or maybe I'll put yours in his and his in yours.
想我去拿水桶吗
Want me to get the bucket?
速度拿来
Kumbaya.
为什么你在特雷司·克鲁塞斯存了这么多钱
So why were you puttin' so much money in Tres Cruces?
因为那是特雷司·克鲁塞斯储贷公司
It's Tres Cruces.
我们以为你只存了一点钱在那里
We thought you just stashed a little cash there
抢劫后却发现了4千万  这怎么回事
until we robbed the place, found 40 million. Why is that?
你们偷了特雷司·克鲁塞斯
You robbed Tres Cruces?
没错  到底怎么回事
That's correct. Why is that?
很好笑是吧  是吗
That's funny, huh?
你死定了
You're dead.
-没错  很好笑是吧  是吧  -你俩都死定了
-Yeah, that is funny, isn't it? -You're both dead.
都不用我动手
And I didn't even have to kill you.
我还以为你是个聪明人  "很有门路"的鲍比
I thought you were sharp. "I-know-a-guy" Bobby.
可你呢...
But you...
你抢的是中情局的钱
You just ripped off the CIA.
中情局
The CIA?
The CIA.
满嘴胡言  中情局存钱的银行  他插一脚干嘛
He's full of crap. Why would he have money in the same bank as the CIA?
你干嘛要把钱存在中情局存钱的银行里
Why would you have money in the same bank as the CIA?
那银行里  我没存一分钱
I don't have shit in that bank.
我在特雷司·克鲁塞斯存的唯一一笔钱
The only money I deliver to Tres Cruces
-是一笔付款  -付给中情局的
-is a payment. -To the CIA?
给中情局  他们从我收入中抽7%
The CIA. They take 7% of my revenue.
作为回报  他们让我用他们的飞机
In return, they let me use their planes
把我的货带出边境
so I can get my shit across the border.
我本来有更便宜的方法  可是他们说了算
I could do it a lot cheaper, but there was really no negotiations.
你知道吗...
You know...
他们收所有党派的贿赂
They take it from all the cartels.
胡说八道
Bullshit.
就算这样
Okay.
他们还是要干掉你俩的
They're still gonna kill you.
鲍比
Bobby?
你说  想来就来的
You said stop by anytime.
-你绑架了一个大毒枭  -没错
-You kidnapped a drug kingpin! -That's correct.
帕皮·格雷科  你还把他捆在我车库里
Papi Greco! And you tied him up in my garage!
你介意我那个酸奶喝吗
You mind if I swipe a yogurt?
没事  拿吧  想拿什么拿什么  全部拿走最好
Yeah, sure. Please. Help yourself to anything. Take whatever you want.
就一罐酸奶而已
It's just a yogurt.
但是她的酸奶  放回去吧
But it's her yogurt. Just put it back.
求你了
Please.
你们两个是前男女朋友吗
Are you two like ex-boyfriend and girlfriend?
实际上  怎么说呢  我们从来没认真谈过
Actually, you know what? We never put a name on it.
那结果呢  你伤他的心  还是他伤了你的心
So, what, you broke his heart or he broke yours?
哇哦  这家伙真是口无遮拦  随便乱问啊
Wow, this guy will really ask anyone anything at anytime.
要不你去看看帕皮的情况  好吗
Why don't you go and check on Papi, huh?
你看上这男人什么了
What do you see in this guy?
我可以说上好几小时  但我不认识你
I could go on for hours, but I don't know you,
我也不觉得我们现在应该
and I don't think this is the right time
谈论这种话题  懂了吗
for us to have this conversation, okay?
所以是恋父情节啦  啊
So daddy issues, huh?
老爸
Daddy!
滚去车库  盯着帕皮  速度滚
Garage. Papi. Go.
-我现在看明白了  -速度滚  滚去车库
-I get it now. -Go. Go to the garage.
-我能拿这罐酸奶吗  -你拿去好了  拿着
-Can I have the yogurt? -You can have the yogurt. Here.
-我不喜欢她  伙计  -没你的事
-I don't like her, man. -You don't get a vote.
我替你盯着她
I'm gonna watch her.
鲍比  你到底在干什么
Bobby. What are you doing?
你完全确定  你能相信那家伙吗
Are you 100% sure you can trust this guy?
不能  但他是我能找到唯一的帮手了
No. But he's all the help I got.
杰瑟普死了
Jessup's dead.
我们偷的是中情局的钱  他们会找上门的
The money we stole was CIA money. They came lookin' for it.
对不起  黛比  我不是故意把你拖下水的
I'm sorry, Deb, I didn't mean to get you involved in all this.
你没事吧
You okay?
你在笑什么呢
What are you smirking at?
你知道吗  我一直挖空心思
You know, I've been racking my brain
想知道你长什么样子的
trying to figure out who you look like.
现在我终于看清楚了
And it finally dawned on me.
你就像墨西哥版的阿尔伯特·爱因斯坦
You look like a Mexican Albert Einstein.
就差点他的智商  这明显的
Minus the genius factor, obviously.
你要点酸奶吗
You want some yogurt?
报复死你俩
Payback's a bitch.
这拳替小托罗打的
That's for Little Toro.
斯蒂格
Stig.
Stig!
打包走人
Pack it up!
这边  这边
Move it, move it!
-斯蒂格  -两个人
-Stig. -The one and only.
是你的人吗
That your people?
你一定要这么说吗
Do you have to say it like that?
怎么说了  他们是你的人  对吧
Like what? They're your people, right?
严格说  是的  但现在只有你是我的人了
Technically, yes, but I thought you were my people now.
好了  数两下  我们就冲进车库  数了啊
All right, two taps, we'll hit the garage. On go.
-好的  你数吧  -动手
-Okay. On your go. -Go!
操
Fuck.
这什么情况
What was that about?
那是一通乱打
That was messed up.
到底什么情况
What the hell is going on?
我不知道
I don't know.
我也不知道
把手机给我  快点
Give me your phone, now.
车子我也要了  出来  出来
I'll take the car, too. Get out. Get out!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
他在辆灰色车上
Está en un gray Charger.
斯蒂格的人怎么知道来你家里找我们的
How did Stig's people know to come to your house?
我不知道  他们肯定是跟踪你们了
I don't know. They must have followed you.
我不觉得
I don't think so.
跟踪的话  我们会发现他们的
We would have seen 'em.
他们肯定发现他们的
We should have seen 'em.
他们怎么知道来你家的
How'd they know to come to your house?
啊
Hmm?
为什么他们来你家了  黛比
Why were they at your house, Debbie?
不是吧  你真的假的
No. You serious?
鲍比...
Bobby...
出去  麻利点
Out of the car, gabacho.
快点
Hurry up.
你现在完了吧
You fucked up now, I see.
跪下
On your knees.
不止你有门路的  鲍比
I know some guys, too, Bobby.
把他们绑起来  带回去再说
Bag 'em up. Let's take 'em home.
-你想谈谈吗  -不用
-Do you wanna talk about it? -No.
-你确定  -我确定
-You sure? -Yeah, I'm sure.
我说了  我不喜欢她  伙计
I told you I didn't like her, man.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你干嘛对我这么态度啊
What are you gettin' mad at me for?
因为你废话太多了
Because you talk too much.
我对你怎么过了啊
What'd I ever do to you?
除了朝我开枪吗
Besides shoot me?
你知道你是什么吗  你就是费青
You know what you are? You're a misanthorpe.
是愤青  我也是个费青
It's misanthrope. I'm a misanthrope.
你知道我说的哪个词吗
Did you know what I meant to say?
不知道  你想说哪个
No. What did you mean to say?
-就是你看谁都不顺眼  -闭嘴
-That you don't like people. -Shut up.
该我松松筋骨了
Time for my massage.
我会替你收拾床的
Yeah. I'll have housekeeping clean up your bed.
靠
Oh, shit.
我爷爷砍了三十年甘蔗  手上从来没出过一个水泡
My grandfather cut cane for 30 years every day and never got a blister.
太难闻了
Says it smells like hell,
不过能让手变得坚韧
toughens the hands.
知道现在我最喜欢什么
You know what I like about this?
我不光能和你俩待在一起
Not only do I get to take my time with you guys,
而且这次不必再担心留下把柄
but this time, I don't have to worry about leaving any marks.
别用你的手碰我
Don't put your hands on me, man.
-靠  -你说什么
-Shit. -What did you say?
别拿你那脏手碰我
Just don't put those pissy hands on me, man.
你无家可归了  鲍比
You ain't got a home, Bobby.
缉毒局不再需要你
DEA doesn't want you around.
因为你犯了罪
Not with your sins.
我到时候报复死你
Payback's a bitch.
你闻起来像臭虫  伙计
You smell like warm Corona, man.
还记得我的牛吧
You remember my prize breeding bull.
它的蛋和椰子一样大
With cojones the size of coconuts.
想见见不
You wanna see him?
不用了  我们在这看就挺好的
No, it's okay. We can see good from here.
拜拜  鲍比
Adiós, Bobby.
别
No, no.
靠
Shit!
4300万美元
43 million!
我们就从CIA那偷了这么多
It's everything we stole from the CIA.
放了我们  我们把钱给你
You let us go, we'll bring it to you.
钱在我这
I got the money.
-你说啥  -钱在我这
-What are you talking about? -I got it.
-钱不在你这  -我当然知道  可他不知道
-You don't have it! -I know I don't have it. He doesn't know that.
可钱不在你手里
But you don't have the money.
我知道钱不在你那  因为在我这
I know you don't have it, 'cause I have it.
在你那  哪儿
You have it? Well, where is it?
昆西司令的保险箱里
Commander Quince's safe.
库帕斯克里斯蒂市海军航空基地
Corpus Christi Naval Air Station.
别跟我说  跟他说
Don't tell me. Tell him.
靠
Oh, shit!
钱在哪
Where is it?
在库帕斯克里斯蒂市海军航空基地昆西司令的保险柜里
Commander Quince's safe! Corpus Christi Naval Air Station!
他就这么侮辱我们  你居然还问要不要告诉他
The guy's pissing on us, and you're askin' if we should fuckin' tell him.
就算你说的是真的  没准我现在也弄死你们
If that's the truth, I might as well just kill you now.
把我女儿带到别的房间去
我正在追查两个从你那出来的家伙
I had a run-in with a couple boys out of your organization.
你好啊  厄尔
Hello, Earl.
鲍比·宾斯先生和迈克尔·斯蒂格曼先生
Mr. Bobby Beans and Mr. Michael Stigman.
他们不是我的人
Well, they're not from my organization.
他们自己单干
They're freelancers.
鲍比·宾斯是缉毒局的间谍
And Bobby Beans is undercover DEA.
斯蒂格曼先生是擅离职守的美国海军
And Mr. Stigman's AWOL U.S. Navy.
他们从特雷司·克鲁塞斯储贷公司偷了4312.5万美元
They stole 43.125 million from the Tres Cruces.
我们想要回来
We want it back.
我有什么好处
Is there a finder's fee?
我们继续让你做生意
Fee is we let you continue to do business.
我们不会把费用从7%提升到20%
Fee is we don't raise our cut from 7% to 20.
我们也不会派一支阿帕奇A-6直升机小队
The fee is we don't come down here
来把你炸的渣都不剩
with a squad of Apache A-6 helicopters
这就是你的好处
and wipe you off the face of the earth.
你希望我的国家脆弱而堕落
You like my country weak and corrupt, don't you?
所以你能在商场里买到便宜的垃圾
So you can buy your cheap crap at the mall.
不过  厄尔  我可不便宜
Well, Earl, I'm not cheap.
你在跟我玩傲气吗
Is this about pride, Manny?
彰显男子气概吗
About machismo?
想要证明你有个巨大的墨西哥屌
Prove you got a big Mexican cock?
不得不说  你的屌确实大
Well, your cock is huge. It's massive.
而且我很敬畏
And I, I'm in awe of your cock.
可那又如何  你还不是个毒贩
So what? You're still a drug dealer.
而我依旧是美国政府的一员
And I'm still the government of the United States.
市场是自由的  曼尼
It's a free market, Manny.
可并不是全世界都如此
Not a free world.
我会想想看
I'll take a look.
你会很为难的
Hard! You'll look hard.
在墨西哥混向来如此
Under every rock in Mexico.
离开这鬼地方
Let's get out of this shithole.
把鸡笼里那俩蠢货放了
如果那白人确实是美国海军  我们没准能赚4300万美元
那你中情局的朋友怎么办
让他回家吃屎去吧
我喜欢这个  老大
我决定让你们去给我带回那4300万美元
I've decided to let you bring me the 43 million.
卡车会带你们向北到边境
The truck'll take you north to the border.
到那以后  你们就得和偷渡者们一起步行穿越国境
From there, you'll cross on foot with the coyotes.
如果一直是这样的话  我们愿意来开车
If it's all the same, we'd rather drive.
现在人人都在找你们
With everybody lookin' for you,
如果开车  他们会在两秒内把你干掉
they'd pull you out of line in two seconds.
所以你们得步行  像我们的人民被迫偷渡一样
No, you go the way you force my people.
如果我们不能冒险穿过边境
If we can't risk crossing,
我们怎么把钱给你带回来
how are we supposed to bring you back the money?
我在北边境等你们24小时
I'll meet you north of the border in 24 hours.
现在  我相信你们不会再讨价还价了
Now, I'm trusting you to fulfill your part of the bargain.
喂  鲍比
Hey, Bobby.
你有24小时把钱给我带来
You got 24 hours to bring me the money.
否则我会在她脑袋上开个洞
Or I'm gonna shoot her right in the head.
然后我会找到你
Then I'm gonna find you,
把你像猪一样开膛破肚
and I'm gonna gut you like a pig!
斯蒂格
Stig!
这些都结束以后  我还是会一枪崩了你
When this is over, I'm still gonna shoot you.
尽管来  鲍比
Whatever it takes, Bobby.
随便挑一辆  我都能弄来
Pick one. I can get in anything.
那辆奥迪怎么样
So, what about the Audi?
不  德国车可不行  锁太复杂  各种警报
No, I don't do German, okay? Locks are tricky, too many alarms.
好吧  雪佛兰厢车怎么样
Okay. Suburban?
那是2010款
That one's 2010.
2英里耗一加仑油  我可不想付那么多油钱
It's gonna get like two miles a gallon. I ain't payin' for all that gas.
作为一个偷车贼  你还真是挑剔
For a car thief, you are mighty particular.
我准备弄那辆本田
I'll break into the Honda.
你看我能和你挤进一辆本田吗
I look like I'm gonna ride in that Honda to you?
你可以的
You could.
那你应该选一辆经典的
And you could pick somethin' with a little more class.
不是我多嘴  我们要闯的可是
I hate to remind you, but we're breakin'
高度戒备的海军基地
onto a high-security Navy base.
不是嘻哈剧院
We ain't goin' to the hip-hop opera.
今晚可没有悲惨世界给你看
It ain't no Les Misérables for you tonight.
悲惨世界
Les Misérables!
随便
Oh, man, whatever the fuck, man.
不用提醒我
Don't remind me.
昆西把钱带到基地可不是我的错
Look, it's not my fault Quince took the money back to the base.
我以为是你把钱带回基地
I thought you said you took the money back to the base.
我从没说过
No, I never said that.
那钱有可能在任何地方
So the money could be anywhere.
可能在东加毕普  在开曼岛
It could be in East Jabip, the Cayman Islands...
不  钱就在基地  好吗
No, the money is on the base, okay?
我在卡米诺瑞尔把钱给了昆西司令
I gave it to Commander Quince at the Camino Real,
然后他让那哥们把钱带回基地
and he told the guys to take it back to the base.
然后他就想弄死你
Right before he took you out and tried to kill you.
那不代表把钱藏基地是故意骗我的
That doesn't mean he's lyin' about the base.
不是所有人都和你一样偏执  鲍比
Not everybody's as paranoid as you, Bobby. Jeez.
那辆普锐斯怎么样  你喜欢不
What about the Prius? You like the Prius?
卡米诺瑞尔
Camino Real.
没错  是个酒店
Yeah, it's a hotel.
我在卡米诺瑞尔遇见了黛比
I met Debbie at the Camino Real.
真的假的
No shit?
-真的  -她在那干嘛
-Yeah. -What was she doin' there?
她说她去那看她男友哈维
She said she was there to meet her boyfriend, Harvey.
等等  你的女朋友还有个男友
Wait. Your girlfriend has a boyfriend?
她不是我女朋友
She's not my girlfriend.
我的天
Holy shit.
赶紧挑辆车吧
Yeah, just pick a car.
就它了
Right here.
就这个
You picked that one?
没错
Yeah.
你还想要啥  宾利
Fuck you want, a fuckin' Bentley?
我来吧
I got it.
-你好  -你好
-Hi. -Hey.
有个问题
Crazy question,
你这有人能修雪地摩托吗
you wouldn't have anybody knows how to fix a snowmobile?
貌似没有
I don't think so.
能不能帮我查一下  今晚之前就得修好
Would you check for me? I really need it fixed by tonight.
怎么  有暴风雪要来
Why, a big storm coming?
谁都不确定它不会来
You never can be too sure.
我去去就来
I'll be right back.
-你咋了  -什么咋了
-Up with that? -What?
她冲你笑  你居然没冲她挤眼睛
She smiled at you, you didn't wink at her?
我可不会冲每一个我看见的女人抛媚眼
I don't wink at every woman I see.
德克萨斯的雪地摩托  看来你要动真格的了
Snowmobile in Texas, huh? You must be in some serious shit, sailor.
你给自己弄了个新爪子
You got yourself a new claw, huh?
-来碰个拳  -挺好看
-Gimme claw. Give it a pound. -It's a beaut.
你这还有我的应急储备吗
You still got my rainy-day stash?
当然
Yeah.
回见  斯蒂格
See ya later, Stig.
好的
All right.
知道人们怎么说吗
You know what they say,
小声说话然后带上M-4和榴弹发射器
talk softly and carry an M-4 with a grenade launcher.
喔
Wow.
你要哪个
Which one you want?
这个
This one.
你有进入基地的计划了吗
What's your plan for gettin' on the base?
正在想
I'm workin' on it.
记住  我们到了指挥楼以后
Remember, once we get to the command building,
昆西的办公室在一楼走廊的最后
Quince's office is first floor, end of the hall.
如果他不在训练场的话  他每天在那住18小时
If he's not in the field, that's where he lives 18 hours a day.
好的  可你还没告诉我
Right, right. But you still haven't told me
你有什么计划能让咱穿过这道门
what the plan is to get through the gate.
我有计划  我是说  我肯定能想到计划
I got a plan. I mean, I'm capable of comin' up with a plan.
我可没说你想不到
I'm not sayin' you're not capable,
我是说你还没告诉我  到底是什么
I'm just sayin' you haven't told me. What is it?
我在想
I'm workin' on it.
最好想快点
Better work faster.
再快点
Much faster.
往前  快点
Move it up. Quickly.
靠
Fuck it.
停下
Halt!
他要闯进去
He's going through!
这够快了不
That fast enough for ya?
靠
Shit!
我们上  电台联系
Let's go! Let's go! On the radio now!
回标杆那去
Return to post!
这就是你的计划
That was your plan?
反正我们已经进来了
Well, we're on the base, aren't we?
这不能叫计划  脑子正常的人都不会闯进一个海军基地
That's not a plan. Nobody in their right mind breaks into a naval base.
这就是计划的高明之处  没人能预料到
That's why it's a brilliant plan. No one expected it.
你应该看看你的表情  他们都和你一样震惊了
You shoulda seen your face. Damn, they were surprised.
你等会下车  我来当诱饵把他们引开
Your stop comin' up. I'll play decoy,
然后去找上将  怎么样
lead 'em away, try to get to the Admiral, okay?
好的  如果出了问题  我们在船坞的院子里见
All right. Things go wrong, I'll see you back at the boat yard.
不会出问题的
Things ain't goin' wrong.
我可以的  我去找上将  我能行  看好
I'm gettin' a medal. I get to the Admiral, I'm gettin' a medal. Watch.
你会祝我好运的对吧
You're gonna wish me luck, aren't ya?
-说啊  -祝你好运
-Come on, man, let's hear it! -Good luck.
昆西的办公室在走廊尽头
Quince's office at the end of the hall.
记住  一楼  走廊尽头
Remember, first floor, end of the hall!
停下  不许动
Halt! Stop where you are!
指挥楼有情况
We have a breach at Status Hall!
快
Go, go, go, go!
上楼
Up the stairs!
长官  士官迈克尔·斯蒂格曼报道  ID号540333
Sir, Petty Officer Michael Stigman, ID number 540333.
等等  出什么问题了
Wait a minute, what's the problem?
对不住  我也不想这么做的
Shit, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that to you, man.
长官
Sir.
我服役12年
I've been in service 12 years.
从来没有踏进过长官食堂  更别提闯进来了
I've never stepped foot in an officers' mess, much less crashed it.
真的  长官  紧急情况
Please, sir, it's an emergency.
去外边等着
Stand outside, please.
-都出去吧  -谢谢  长官
-Leave us alone. -Thank you, sir.
真对不住
Hey, I'm really sorry about that, man.
我确实没想打你来着  我道歉
I didn't mean to hit you like that. I apologize.
说吧  士官  坐
I'm listening, sailor. Sit.
谢谢  长官
Thank you, sir.
-接着帮我拨将军的电话  -是  长官
-Try the Admiral again for me. -Yes, sir.
你相信这些偷出来的钱
And you believed this stolen money
可被用来打击毒品团伙
would all be used to fight drug cartels?
是的  长官  我认为结果取决于有效的指挥
Yes, sir. I thought the orders came down the valid chain of command.
愚忠非忠
Blind loyalty is not loyalty.
我明白  长官  这就是我来这的原因
I know that, sir, and that's why I'm here.
你能到这来告诉我这个说明你胆子很大
Well, you've shown a lot of tenacity
也很有韧性
and a lot of guts bringing this to me.
谢谢  长官  因为您能挽救这一切
Thank you, sir. That means the world comin' from you.
不幸的是对这事我无能为力
Unfortunately, there's nothing I can do for you.
当然可以  长官  您只需关闭基地
Of course, sir. I mean, you can just lock down the base.
可以逮捕昆西司令
You can arrest Commander Quince.
美国海军不会抢银行
The United States Navy does not rob banks.
我们的人从来没有抢过银行
Its personnel did not rob a bank.
我不会因为一个坏士兵而玷污美国海军的正直形象
I'm not gonna tarnish the integrity of the Navy over one crooked sailor.
如果银行丢了钱
If there was money taken from the bank
那肯定是不合法的中情局的破基金的钱
that was part of an illegal CIA slush fund,
而海军根本就不知道这个基金的存在
the Navy had no knowledge the fund existed.
你的档案还是六个月的擅离职守
Your jacket has you six months AWOL?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
那它一直都会这样了
It's gonna stay that way.
昆西司令的档案也会被修改成擅离职守
Commander Quince's jacket will likewise be amended so he's also AWOL,
这样就不会是海军的问题了
making none of this the Navy's problem.
长官  这么做不对
Sir, this isn't right.
我可以提供更多
Well, I'd offer more,
但是当手臂已经坏疽
but when the hand has gangrene,
断臂才能活命
you chop it off to save the body.
你不能因为它本来是好的就一直留着
You don't keep the pinkie around just because it meant well.
把士官斯蒂格曼请出大门外边去
Have Petty Officer Stigman dropped outside the main gate.
要是他再走进世界上任何一个军事基地
He sets foot on a military base anywhere in the world,
毙了他
I want him shot.
全是扯淡
This is bullshit.
士兵听从你这样的人的命令去战斗至死
You know, men like me fight and die on the orders of men like you!
没有我们  你肩膀上的星星就是戏服
Without us, those stars on your shoulder are a fucking costume!
打开保险箱
Open the safe.
你老大知道你在这吗
Does your boss know you're doin' this?
打开
Open it.
还是中情局把她杀了  就像他们杀了杰瑟普
Or did the CIA kill her like they did Jessup?
和你有什么关系
What's it to you?
我不喜欢模糊的结局
I don't like loose ends.
我也不喜欢
Neither do I...
哈维
Harvey.
是吧
Huh?
我妈叫我霍华德
Well, my mother named me Harold.
我觉得哈维更好听
I like Harvey. Harvey has a nice ring to it.
你不喜欢哈维
Don't you like Harvey?
-我不知道你在说什么  -你当然知道
-I don't know what you're talkin' about. -Yes, you do.
最近去过卡米诺瑞尔酒店吧
Been to the Camino Real Hotel lately?
打开保险箱
Open the safe.
集结地已就绪
Staging area cleared up!
可以通过
Bring it through!
钱在哪
Where's the money?
你先告诉我黛比在哪
You tell me where Deb is.
她在做指甲  钱在哪
She's gettin' her nails done. Where is the money?
我不知道
I don't know.
好了  现在告诉我你所做的
All right, tell me what you do know.
你女朋友和我
Well, your girl found out where the CIA
同时发现了中情局藏钱的地方
was stashing the money right about when I did.
当我告诉她
And when I told her
我俩可以陷害你和斯蒂格曼然后带着钱远走高飞的时候
that she and I could get away with the money by setting you and Stigman up,
她连眼睛都没眨一下
she didn't even blink.
别骗我
Don't lie to me.
她和你在一起就那么不开心
Was she that unhappy, Bobby?
钱在哪  别骗我
Where is the money? Don't lie to me.
你和斯蒂格曼还活着  你觉得我会把钱放这
You think I'd keep it here with you and Stigman still alive?
别傻了  鲍比
Come on, Bobby.
你把钱给她了  是吗
You gave it to her, didn't you?
是吗
Didn't you?
将军  向后退
Commander. Back up.
-快快快  -在你们六点钟方向
-Go, go, go, go! -On your six!
快  快  快
Move, move, move!
所有人员从大厦内撤离
All personnel evacuate the building.
看住后门  在草丛里
Take the back, in that alley!
去前门  我们走
Go to the front! Let's go!
闪开点
Hey!
这边  行动
This way! Move!
快点  跟上  我们得找到他
Come on, come on! Find him!
没有发现
Clear!
你还好吗
You Okay?
快点起来  我们走
Come on, let's go.
还好吗  先生  是的  我没事
You okay, sir? Yeah, I'm fine.
他从下水管逃走了
Work off the standpipe!
这烧烤做的真不错
This is really good barbecue.
你肯定想尝尝吧
You don't want to regret not tryin' it.
为什么你还在这浪费时间不直接杀了我呢
Why don't you stop wasting my time and just kill me?
就算鲍比带着钱来了
Even if Bobby was coming with the money,
你还是会把我们都杀了吧
you'd still kill us both.
但是他不会来了
But he's not coming.
-他会来的  -不会了
-He'll be here. -No.
他不会来了
He won't.
你觉得他会不管你死活吗
You think he's just gonna let you die?
你觉得海军跑到我家来找鲍比是巧合吗
You think it was a coincidence the Navy came looking for Bobby at my house?
如果不是鲍比  至少我已经拿到4300万的一半
If I couldn't have Bobby, at least I'd have half of 43 million.
是你给鲍比·宾斯下的套
You set up Bobby Beans.
不然我也不会来找你的
I wouldn't be coming for you either.
钱在哪里
Where's the money?
别傻了  我也不知道
Come on. I don't know.
钱已经汇到国外了
Gone, outta the country.
肯定不在海军总部  帕皮
It's certainly not on a Navy base, Papi.
那里都给了你什么
Where does that leave you?
给了我应得的
Exactly where I deserve to be.
-是我  -鲍比
-Yeah. -Bobby.
你迟到了
You're late.
我拿到钱了
I got the money.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
我这次真的拿到了
No, I got it.
相信我  我真的拿到钱了  我这就拿来给你
Believe me, I got it. I'll bring it to you.
你在哪里
Where are you?
嗨  鲍比
Hi, Bobby.
黛比
Debbie?
他能听到我们说话吗
Can he hear us?
挂了电话快逃
Just hang up the phone and run.
好的  听我说
Okay, listen to me.
告诉他我拿到钱了
Tell him I got the money.
快挂电话
Hang up the phone.
不是你的错  只是...
It's not your fault. Just...
黛比
Debbie.
告诉他我拿到钱了  好吗
Tell him I have the money. Okay?
而且我知道钱在哪里
And I know you know where the money is.
一定要告诉他我拿到了
Just tell him I have it.
黛比  听我说
Debbie, listen to me.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很爱你
I really meant to love you.
黛比
Debbie.
黛比  你在哪儿  黛比  你在哪
Where are you? Debbie, where are you?
黛比告诉我你在哪儿
Where are you? Debbie?
你还在听吗
Hello?
还在吗
黛比  听我说  嗯...
Hello? Debbie? Uh...
再等一分钟  我拿到钱了
Wait a minute, I got the money.
他们怎么说  海军上将怎么说
What'd they say? What'd the Admiral say?
上将能怎么说  上将已经把自己撇的干干净净了
What'd the Admiral say? Admiral washed his hands of the whole thing.
海军完全坐视不理
Navy turned their back.
那钱呢
Where's the money?
没有钱了  斯蒂格
There was no money, Stig.
什么  没钱了
What? There was no money.
当然有钱  我把钱给了昆西
'Course there is. I gave Quince the money.
是的  然后昆西给了黛比  现在黛比死了
Right, and Quince gave it to Deb, and Deb is dead.
帕皮杀了他
Papi killed her.
狗日的
Fuck him.
那我们一起去墨西哥
Let's go down to Mexico.
我们要把他们一个个揪出来  然后把他们全干掉
We'll lure 'em all down, then take every one of 'em out. Kill 'em all.
然后呢
And then what?
至少要干掉昆西和帕皮
Well, at least Quince and Papi'd be dead.
再然后呢
And then what?
你想让他们逍遥法外吗
Oh, you just wanna let 'em skate?
是你不明白吧  斯蒂格
You don't get it, do ya, Stig?
上帝啊  你还按自己直觉行事吗
I mean, God bless you, you still think there's some kinda code.
根本就没有直觉
There is no code.
你只是遵循着海军给你的每个命令  他们耍得你团团转
You followed every order the Navy gave you, they kicked you in the teeth.
根本就没有什么直觉  斯蒂格
There is no code, Stig.
没人为了海军拼命  懂吗  根本就不关海军的事
No one fights for the Navy, okay? It's not about the Navy.
你是为了身边的伙伴而拼命
You fight for the guy that's fighting next to you.
这对你来说没有意义吗
That doesn't mean anything to you?
我要去墨西哥了
I'm goin' to Mexico.
还有你知道吗  我的直觉救了你的命
And just so you know, my code saved your life.
在你心脏和肩膀之间三英尺的地方
There's three inches between your heart and your shoulder.
我的子弹如果再左偏三英尺  你早死了
My bullet goes three inches left, you'd be dead.
我也不会在这里
And I wouldn't be here.
昆西要杀了我  因为我让你活了下来
'Cause Quince only decided to kill me because I let you live.
你以为我当时是失手吗
What, you think I missed, huh?
你是这样想的吗  你以为是我失手了
Is that what you think? You think I missed?
你什么时候见我失手过
When have you ever seen me miss?
你就呆在这儿吧  我要去墨西哥了
You stay here. I'm goin' to Mexico.
我们的约定还有效吗
Our deal still stand?
我给你钱  你帮我跑路
I give you the money, I walk away clean?
好热闹  看起来你早上起的很早啊
Hola. Looks like you had a banner morning.
你最好弄到钱了
You better have my money.
就在这里  一个子不差
Right here. Every penny.
鲍比在哪里
Where's Bobby?
我们两分道扬镳了
We had a philosophical fallin' out.
把你的后箱打开
Open your trunk.
我只是想要你一句话还有你的兄弟们
I just want your word that you and your boys,
费雷·诺斯·胡里奥  他们所有人
Ferret Nose Julio, all of 'em,
你们都要帮我干掉昆西司令
you'll help me kill Commander Quince.
谁是昆西司令
Who's Commander Quince?
那就是他
That's him.
斯蒂格曼先生  你承诺给我四千三百万
Mr. Stigman, you promised me $43 million
如果我杀了这里的所有人
for killin' everyone on this ranch.
你的钱就在这里  先生
Got the money right here, sir.
问题是  我也承诺了给帕皮四千三百万
Thing is, I promised Papi the $43 million, too,
所以恐怕你们二位要自己解决问题了
so I'm afraid you two are gonna have to duke it out.
也许我们会先杀了你然后把这笔钱分了
Maybe he and I'll just kill you instead and split the money.
你觉得怎么样  帕皮
What do you say, Papi?
一个人两百万
50% of 40 million?
总比死了好  不是吗
Better than 100% dead, right?
他肯定是在唬你  等你一转身  马上干掉你
He'll double-cross you. Minute your back is turned, bullet in the head.
五五分账
50-50.
楼顶上的说要四六分
The guy up on the roof says 60-40.
他的话没一句准信
He ain't got a trustworthy bone in his body.
他说要干掉我  我不又回来了
I came back, didn't I?
狗日的中情局
Fuckin' CIA.
好热闹  好热闹
Red rover, red rover.
哪位仁兄拿了我的4312.5万块  快给我交回来
Whoever's got my 43.125 million better come the fuck on out.
你也叫他来收钱了
You offer him the money, too?
我可没叫上他
I didn't call him.
钱在后车厢里
It's in the trunk!
你干嘛把钱在哪儿告诉他
Why the fuck did you tell him that?
多谢你  指挥官
Thank you, Commander.
斯蒂格曼先生  快给我把后车厢打开
Mr. Stigman, come on out and open the trunk.
慢慢的来哦
Nice and slow, now.
看来我们又有新客人了
Well, what do we got here?
听起来好像一个墨西哥婚礼哦
Sounds like a Mexican wedding.
这不是我的64年雪佛兰
Is that my '64 Impala?
正是
That's correct.
我告诉过你
I told you.
我门路广着呢
I know a guy.
现在
Now,
谁想看看四千三百万现金
who wants to see $43 million?
终于出现了  你可是让我找得好苦啊
For a minute there, I thought you had me chasing my tail.
你想数数吗
You want to count it?
你如果想耍花招  我绝对能找到你
If you're shortin' me, I know where to find you.
所以我们没事了咯
So we're good?
我不是跟你说过了吗
Did I not give you my word?
是的没错
That's right.
那就别像个傻子一样对我
Then don't treat me like an asshole.
我尽力
I'll try my best.
你和斯蒂格曼先生可以走了
You and Mr. Stigman are free to go.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
我相信你们能找到回家的路吧
I trust you can find your own way home?
肯定的
That's right.
-你在干什么  鲍比  -我们走
-What're you doing, Bobby? -Let's go.
我不能让他们拿走那笔钱
I'm not gonna let him get away with the money.
我们走  我恨那些走狗
Let's go. I hate these daggone teeth.
他们不会这样放我们走的
They're not just gonna let us go.
-我心里有数  -嘿  我都带了我的M-16
-I got a plan. -Hey, I got my M-16.
我还带了榴弹发射器和M-4  我们为什么不和他们干
I got my grenade launcher, I got my M-4. Let's do this shit.
我自有安排  我来这里怎么会没有准备
I got a plan. I'm capable of coming up with a plan.
好吧  最好别让我失望
Well, it better be a goddamn good one.
你肯定会喜欢的
It's a good plan.
要下雨咯
Make it rain.
这就是你的计划  炸飞四千三百万前进
That was your plan? To blow up $43 million?
是的  这就是我计划的高明之处  没人料得到
Yeah, that's why it's a brilliant plan. Nobody expected it.
快走
Go.
快点  跟上
Come on, move it!
该死  快走
Dumb assholes! Move it!
你不来
You comin'?
当然来  我就在后面跟着你
Go ahead, I'll be right behind you.
别打飞了
Don't miss.
我从来不会失手
I never miss!
我就说吧
Told ya.
斯蒂格  斯蒂格
Stig! Stig!
别动手  别动手
Don't do it. Don't do it.
游戏时间结束了
Playtime's over.
别再跟我兜圈子了
No more fucking around.
现在
Now,
丢掉你的武器
drop your weapon.
让斯蒂格曼也照做
Tell Mr. Stigman to do the same.
你跟他说吧
You tell him.
现在很清楚
It's real simple.
要么我们都放下枪要么我们都去死
We can all make a deal or we can all die.
我可不想这样
I'm not making any deals.
和你的人好好说说  鲍比
Talk to your man, Bobby.
别犯傻
Be the smart one.
你觉得特雷司·克鲁塞斯是我们唯一存钱的地方吗
You think Tres Cruces is the only stash we got?
我们有20多处金库  倒处都是钱
We got 20 more. We got money everywhere.
你什么都改变不了
You're not gonna change a damn thing.
斯蒂格
Stig?
怎么说
Yeah?
你是我的人  对吗
You're my people, right?
那是当然
That's correct.
你还好吗
You good?
没法更好了
Never better.
我们不是一般人  所以
We're not people, though.
所以我们是一家人
This makes us family.
好的  兄弟
All right, brother.
嘿  墨西哥爱因斯坦
Hey, se?or Einstein,
你看起来状况很糟糕哦  老兄
you're looking kind of fucked up sittin' there, man.
你们还好吗
You all right?
帮我好好割草
Mow my lawn.
你知道什么事情超酷吗
Well, you know what was so cool?
你开着64年的雪佛兰进来真是太棒了
You rolling in on that '64 Impala.
你看起来就是坏小子一个哦
I mean, you looked badass, man.
那是肯定的
Yeah, that's right.
听着  还有一件事  还有一件事
Listen, one more thing, one more thing.
啥事
What?
把你的枪给我
Give me your gun.
你不是认真的吧
You're not serious.
我是认真的
Yes, I am.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们经历了那么多事  你真的要这样做吗
You're really gonna do this after everything we've been through?
手臂还是大腿
Arm or leg?
这不会让你好受些的
This is not gonna make you feel better.
我想还是腿好  因为腿上肉更多  这样不会伤到骨头
I'm thinking leg. Because leg, there's more flesh, there's not as much bone.
手臂就可能...
The arm will...
你知道吗  你简直就是个...
You know what you are? You are a petty...
狗娘养的
Fucking son of a bitch!
很痛啊  你知道吗  要是搞不好你可能害死我啊
Hurts, doesn't it? You know you coulda killed me?
不会吧  再向左三英尺你才会死呢
Is that right? Three more inches to the left.
这完全是两码事好吗
Don't even say it, man.
你不会再对服务生抛媚眼了吧
You wouldn't be winking at waitresses anymore.
我还是会的  我总是不能自已
I'd still wink, I just wouldn't be able to do anything about it.
你知道我的  我从不失手
You know me, I don't miss.
-我从来不会失手  -你上次看到我失手是什么时候
-I never miss. -When's the last time you saw me miss?
你这下一路都得背着我了
You gonna carry my ass all the way the fuck home.
嘿  慢点  很疼哎
Oh, shit, man. This burns.
那就对了
That's correct.
你知道  我向你开枪的时候我还不知道你是谁呢
You know, I shot you when I didn't know who you were.
我们是一家人之前
Before we were family.
但是现在不一样了
There's a difference.
但我们现在是一家人  我向你开枪因为我知道你是谁了
But we're family now. I shot you because I know who you are.
这就不对了
That ain't right.
他们肯定看到了
They definitely got the look.
防风墨镜加上那副臭脸  绝对是中情局的人
Assholes and windshield sunglasses, practically CIA uniform.
你们还要吃点什么吗
Can I get you boys anything else?
我想试试你们的甜甜圈
Are your doughnuts any good?
跟你说实话吧  甜甜圈味道真的一般
Tell you the truth, they're pretty lousy.
听到这个消息真是太好了  看来你没戏咯
Can't tell you how happy we are to hear that.
欢迎下次再来
You take care.
我看到了哦
I saw that.
-看到什么了  -你抛媚眼了
-Saw what? -You winked.
-那个叫勾引  -好吧  是的
-That's a twitch. -Yeah, right.
你知道的  对于一个刚刚炸飞四千三百万的人来说
You know, for a guy who just blew up $43 million,
你给的小费倒是不少啊
all of a sudden, you are a very generous tipper.
谁说我炸飞了四千三百万
Who said I blew up $43 million?
你在说什么呢
What are you sayin'?
我什么都没说  你听到了啥呀
I'm not sayin' anything. What are you hearing?
我听到了我很感兴趣的事  你刚刚说了
I'm hearin' somethin'. You're sayin' somethin'.
好吧  如果你听到了  那么说明只是你听到了
Well, if you're hearin' it, it's only because you're hearin' it,
我可啥都没说
not 'cause I'm sayin' it.
你留了多少
How much did you keep?
两百万
Two million?
我们一人能有一百万哦
That's like one each.
所以你拿一半
So now you get half?
-你看  我打死了一半的人  -那又怎样
-Well, I shot half the guys. -So?
真的是两百万
Two million?
最新电影大片首发 请访问
新气息论坛 www.xinqixi.com